ILGWU Political Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/119
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Political Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers
1964-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Dubrow, Evelyn
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780/119
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection contains Evelyn Dubrow's correspondence, memoranda, and reports relating to the her lobbying activities in Washington, D.C., as well as letters and receipts documenting campaign contributions, and files on states, local unions, joint boards, and regional departments.
5516691
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
C. Berne, August 07, 2009
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 15, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Evelyn Dubrow was born in Passaic, New Jersey, in 1911. A graduate of New York University, Dubrow worked as a report for The Morning Call (Patterson, N.J.) and Secretary of the New Jersey organization of the American Newspaper Guild from 1943 to 1946, before becoming Educational Director for the Textile Workers Union of American in New Jersey. In 1949, she became New York state Director for Americans for Democratic Action. In 1956, she was named the ILGWU's chief lobbyist in Washington, D.C. Dubrow worked as Legislative Representative and Executive Secretary of the Political Department of the ILGWU, and continued her work after the union's merger with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers of America to create the Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE). Dubrow died in Washington D.C., in 2006.
Biographical / Historical
The Political Department of the ILGWU was founded in 1947, under the direction of Gus Tyler. Its primary function was to engage union members and their families in political issues at the local, state, and national levels. This engagement was achieved through conferences, publications, and other communications. Educational work was a hallmark of the department, as were the department's legislative monitoring, research activities, and organizing for electoral campaigns.
David Wells joined the Political Department in 1952, eventually becoming Assistant Director. In 1956, Evelyn Dubrow was named the ILGWU's chief lobbyist in Washington, D.C., and became a well-known fixture on Capitol Hill.
Scope and Contents
The Political Department records are constituted of two accessions of Evelyn Dubrow papers and one accession of records from the department. Included are correspondence and memoranda, reports of lobbying activities, subject files on states and ILGWU affiliates, receipts for campaign contributions, ephemera from political campaigns.
These records are complemented by one accession of the Gus Tyler papers (5780/088) that includes records relating to his work as founding director of the Political Department, in addition to some of his other activities relating to the union. An oral history interview with David Wells (6036/076), in which the former Assistant Director discusses his work with the Union and in New York City, also complements the records of the Political Department.
Taken together, these materialsthe Political Department records, Evelyn Dubrow papers, Gus Tyler papers, and the David Wells interviewdocument a considerable range of the Political Department's work from its founding in 1948 to its merger with ACTWU in 1995.
This collection contains Evelyn Dubrow's correspondence, memoranda, and reports relating to the her lobbying activities in Washington, D.C. Also included in this collection are letters and receipts documenting campaign contributions, alphabetical files on states, as well as files on local unions, joint boards, and regional departments. The records of the Political Department also contain ephemeral printed material relating to political campaigns, including pamphlets, posters, and fliers.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/103: ILGWU Political Department Records 5780/142: ILGWU Political/Legislative Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/088: ILGWU Gus Tyler Papers 6036/076 OH: Daniel Soyer ILGWU Heritage Project 6036/080: Evelyn Dubrow papers 6036/080 P: Evelyn Dubrow Photographs
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; Dubrow, Evelyn.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Political Dept.
5516691
- Anti-Import Rally Joint ILG/ACTWY, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  April 13
- Anti-Import Rally Joint ILG/ACTWY, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Film Notes (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "G" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "H" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Women's Leadership Rally on National Health Insurance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Health Security, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "I" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Reception, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Replies from Congressmen on 807, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence on 807, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Correspondence on 807, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Campaign for Repeal of 807, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Informal House Textile Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "J" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- "K" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Labor General, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- "L" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lobbying Reports (Evelyn Dubrow), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Lobbying Reports (Pam Freer), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- "N" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Letters from Members, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- "M" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- National Consumer League, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- National Legislative Conference, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  January 19-21
- National Staff Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- National Staff Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- National Sharecroppers, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- "O" General, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- "P" General, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Replies on HR 11552 - Postcard Voter Registration Act, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "R" General, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "S" General, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Senate, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Senior Citizens, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- "T" General, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Bayh's Amendment to Tax Bill to Preserve Sick Pay Exclusion for Low and Middle Income Taxpayers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Tax Reform Bill (HR 10612), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- "U" General, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Union Label Advertisements, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- "W" General, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence to Evelyn Dubrow, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- "XYZ" General, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Radio - 1964 Campaign (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Radio - 1968 Campaign (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 1968 Campaign Committee Posters and Mats (Box 2, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Radio Campaign Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Campaign Literature, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  In English and Spanish
- 1968 Election - General (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 1968 Election - General (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Humphrey for President Material, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Registration Information, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- 1968 Election Memos, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Podell Campaign Bills, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Cope PA Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Thank You Letters from Candidates for Contributions Received, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Wires of Congratulations from President Stulberg to Candidates who were Elected, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Senator Harrison Williams' Campaign in New Jersey, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Lists for Thank You Letters, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Final Reports, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Campaign Literature, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Bank and Investments, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Replies from Members of Cope Operating Committee on Arthur Berger Campaign, etc., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Congressional Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Congressional Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Campaign Committee Set-up, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Form Letters, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Campaign Committee, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Requests for Contributions, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Contributions - General, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Contribution to the 1970-1971 Democratic Congressional and Senatorial Dinner (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Paid Bills, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Campaign Set-up, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Inter-Office, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Form Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Letters Requesting Orders for Spanish Leaflets (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Locals who have set up Campaign Committees, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Cope, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Central States, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Studds for Congress Campaign, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee and Senatorial Committee, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Democratic Study Group, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Cloak Joint Board and Cloak Out-of-Town, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Eastern Region, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Midwest Region, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- New York City Locals, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Northeast Department, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Ohio-Kentucky, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Philadelphia Dress Joint Board, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Southeast Region, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Upper South Department, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Western States, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Requests for Contributions, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Campaign Correspondence, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Contributions - Alabama, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Contributions - Alaska, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Contributions - California, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Contributions - Colorado, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Contributions - Connecticut, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Contributions - Delaware, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Contributions - Florida, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Contributions - Georgia, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Contributions - Hawaii, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Contributions - Idaho, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Contributions - Illinois, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Contributions - Indiana, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Contributions - Iowa, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Contributions - Kansas, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Kentucky, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Louisiana, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Contributions - Maine, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Contributions - Massachusetts, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Contributions - Maryland, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Contributions - Michigan, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Contributions - Minnesota, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Contributions - Mississippi, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Contributions - Missouri, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Contributions - Montana, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Contributions - New Hampshire, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Contributions - New Mexico, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Contributions - New Jersey, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Contributions - New York, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Contributions - North Carolina, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Contributions - North Dakota, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Contributions - Ohio, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Contributions - South Dakota, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Contributions - Oklahoma, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Contributions - Oregon, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Contributions - Pennsylvania, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Contributions - Rhode Island, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Contributions - South Carolina, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Contributions - Tennessee, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Contributions - Texas, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Contributions - Utah, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Contributions - Vermont, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Contributions - Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Contributions - West Virginia, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Contributions - Washington, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Contributions - Wisconsin, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Contributions - Wyoming, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Thank You Letters to Staff Members for Work on Rally, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Candidates in 1972 Elections (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Thank You Letters to Local Union Managers for Work on Campaign, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Letters of Congratulations to Members of the House and Senate who were Elected and Re-elected, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Federal Campaign Election Act, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Thank You Letters to People Who Worked on November 1st Rally, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Miscellaneous State Laws, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Arizona, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Connecticut, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Kentucky, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Maryland, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Montana, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - New Hampshire, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - New Jersey, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - New York, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Ohio, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Pennsylvania, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Washington, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Wisconsin, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- State Law Filings and Registrations - Wyoming, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Hazleton District Council Campaign Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Northern New England District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Scranton District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Southern New England District, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Shamokin/Sunbury District Council, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Trenton/Wilmington District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Local 324 Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Local 351 Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Local 361 Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Boston Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Central Pennsylvania District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Easton District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Local 10, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Local 66 Campaign Fund, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Local 98 Campaign Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Eastern Region, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Cloak Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Dress Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Northeast Department, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Local 93, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Local 111, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Local 178, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Locals 185-306, 1972-1976 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Local 226, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Local 295, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Local 20, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Local 20, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Upstate New York and Vermont District Council, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Western Massachusetts District Council, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Western Pennsylvania District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Wyoming Valley District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Knit Goods Union Local 190 Campaign Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Philadelphia Dress Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Midwest Region, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Eastern Missouri Political Education League, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Kansas City Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Missouri, Kansas, Nebraska, Iowa, and Minnesota District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- St. Louis Joint Board, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Southern Illinois District Council, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Southern Missouri-Arkansas Political Education League, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Texoma Political Action League, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Southeast Region, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Upper South Department, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- San Francisco Joint Board, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Western States Region, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Democratic Party, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- United States Department of Justice, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Department of Agriculture (Food Stamps), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- United States Department of State, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- "E" General, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- "F" General, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Facts About Congress, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Federal Election Campaign Act Amendments, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Labor Law Reform H.R. 8410, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Labor - General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- "L" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- "K" General, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- "J" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- National Civic Review, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- National Consumers League, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- National Municipal League, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- National Sharecroppers, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- New York City, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- "O" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- "P" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- "R" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- "S" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Senate - General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- "I" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- "U" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- "W" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Evelyn Dubrow, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- "Y" General, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Justice, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Justice, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- AFL-CIO News, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Inter-Office, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Form Letters, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Central States Region, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Cloak Joint Board and Cloak Out-of-Town, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Eastern Region, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Midwest Region, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- New York City Locals, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- New England Region, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Northeast Department, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Ohio-Kentucky Region, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Southeast Region, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- South Jersey-Philadelphia Joint Board, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Upper South, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Western States, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- January, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- February, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- March, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- April, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- May, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- June, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- July, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- August, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- September, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- October, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- November, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- December, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- "A" General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- AFL-CIO General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO Cope General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Cope Area Conferences, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO IUD General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- "B" General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- "C" General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Center for the Family, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- The Citizens Conference on State Legislatures, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Civil Rights, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Congress - General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- "D" General, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Democratic National Committee, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- "B" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- "C" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- CETA, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Citizens Union, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Coalition of Labor Union, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women Legislative Conference, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  September 15-18
- Congressional Lunch and Fashion Show, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  May 21
- Congress - General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Replies from Congressmen and Senators on Hong Kong Article, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Consumer Federation of America, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Consumer Assembly, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Convention Report (Box 9, Folder 13)
- "D" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Day Care and Child Development Council of America, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Democratic National Committee, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Democratic Study Group, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- "E" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- "F" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- "G" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- "H" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- "I" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Inauguration, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- International Women's Year, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  Albany, New York
- Pam Freer Lobbying Reports, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Pamela Freer Expenses, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Evelyn Dubrow Expenses, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Minimum Wage, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- "M" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- "N" General, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- International Women's Year, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  Houston, Texas
- Lobbying Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Legislative Newsletter, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Legislative Bulletin, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Inter-Office, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Form Letters, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Political Department Invoices, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Central States, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Eastern Region, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Midwest, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- New England Region, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- New York Locals, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- New York State, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 9)